Speaker 1: Alicia Silverstone just dropped a nuclear bomb in Hollywood's lap and all hell is breaking loose. She released the Hospital Bed Confession, where Courtney Love admits she's been addicted for years to the pure liquid
Speaker 2: rush of adrenochrome. She says it's 100 times better than heroin.
OK,
Speaker 3: guys, so she thought she was dying and poured her soul
out,
Speaker 4: confessed to everything, and...
Speaker 4: It's all on tape. It's insane and disgusting. So, yeah, don't say I didn't warn
you.
Speaker 1: Courtney Love's hospital bed confession gets even worse. She admits on tape that she ate dozens of children to prove loyalty, to stay in the Illuminati. That tape is now public.
and
Speaker 1: all hell is breaking loose as we speak. Courtney's response: Instagram post damage control full meltdown threats that
Speaker 5: works. Um, I almost
Speaker 6: died. I lost all my hair, I was about a hundred pounds, and they told me I was going to die.
Speaker 2: Courtney Love has been hiding in plain sight for decades. First, she was exposed in Jeffrey Epstein's Little Black Book. Her name was circled with multiple contact numbers, meaning she was a key contact.
Speaker 2: Then, the Epstein files dropped and she was exposed as one of Hollywood's most prolific cannibals, who spent years indulging her appetite for the sickest vices known to man: child meat and adrenochrome. Fast forward to today, Alicia Silverstone just took to Instagram to release a leaked video featuring Courtney Love in hospital, writhing in pain,
Speaker 2: believing she's breathing her lost breaths and confessing her most
Speaker 7: depraved secrets.
-
Speaker 4: Um, so, Courtney Love is dying of Kuru,
you guys.
Speaker 4: The cannibal disease. The one that eats freaking holes in your brain. Like, literal holes. And the only way to get it? Eating infected
Speaker 3: human flesh. That's the only way, period. So,
Speaker 3: You know, do the math.
Speaker 8: We've got Courtney's hospital bed confession coming
Speaker 9: right up. But first, Alicia explains why she had to share it with her most loyal supporters and those who were determined to hold the elite to account. Look at
Speaker 4: the symptoms: blindness, hair loss, wasting away. Same as Ariana Grande, same as Celine, same as Ellen, same as Demi. Exact same, you guys.
And
Speaker 10: I just, I think we need to talk about this, like actually talk about
it.
Speaker 2: - The same industry elites who flew with Epstein, partied in his circle and sustained their youth through the worst crimes imaginable, are
Speaker 1: now facing a reckoning, both private and public. Brace yourself, we're now seconds away from the moments the mask came off. When Courtney Love thought she was taking her final breaths, when she thought that she was seconds away from being
Speaker 2: dragged straight into hell for all eternity,
and
Speaker 2: when she broke completely and confessed the truth. But first, just quickly, the internet isn't a world frontier anymore. Israel has infiltrated the world's leading VPNs, ExpressVPN, CyberGhost, Nord, Private Internet Access, and dozens more. As for Proton, it's funded and controlled by the World Economic Forum. Using legacy VPNs in 2026 is wiring yourself straight into the surveillance matrix. That's why we're revealing the first trustless
VPN,
Speaker 2: vp.net forward slash tpv trust is obsolete this is math next-gen privacy that makes spying impossible even for the people who built it even for the feds and trust me they've tested it came up empty every single time how do you think we're still on the air
sign up
Speaker 2: today at vp.net forward slash tpv now back to courtney
She
Speaker 2: wasn't suffering from some unknown illness. She was in debilitating adrenochrome withdrawal. Kuru had begun eating her brain from the inside
out,
Speaker 11: destroying her body, her mind and what was left of her soul. In that raw terrifying moment, she admitted everything.
I ate
Speaker 12: children, so many kids, man, so many.
Speaker 13: And the blood, I drank so much blood. It's better than heroin.
Speaker 13: Uh, uh, like a hundred times better. A thousand. I'm so f***ed. I'm so f***ing f***ed. I'm gonna burn for
Speaker 14: this. Oh, I know I am.
Speaker 1: Courtney didn't die. She didn't meet her maker. Not that day at least. Because Hollywood has an emergency cure. Fresh adrenochrome from highly terrorized child victims. One dose and she was back on her feet.
Speaker 1: Feeling like a million bucks you want
Speaker 4: to sue me? Okay, fine. Let's do discovery because I know everything about that hospital visit
I have the
Speaker 4: receipts like actual receipts Ah And when we release the rest of this tape Hollywood is gonna burn And I'm not even
kidding
-
Speaker 1: Courtney didn't waste a second. Monday morning, the damage control machine kicked in. Emergency Instagram
Speaker 2: posts, narrative spin, and full crisis mode. She admitted that she almost died in 2019. Carefully chosen words, carefully crafted confession, just enough truth to bury
Speaker 15: the rest.
Speaker 16: - I went to England in 2018, and when I went
there,
You
Speaker 6: know, my body just exploded, it just exploded. And I was in hospitals a lot, I almost died. I lost all my hair, I was about a hundred pounds and they told me I was gonna
Speaker 2: die. - Exact same symptoms. To those who are not in the know, the post looked innocent, album update, nothing to see here. But then she started speaking in code words, the same cannibal language that spilled out of the Epstein files.
Speaker 2: This is where it gets really dark. You don't want to miss this. But first, Courtney Love didn't just eat kids to stay in the Illuminati. She was a participant in an industry built on their suffering. An industry promoted by Hollywood, protected by the media, and enabled by the powerful names redacted in the Epstein files. When she talks about red, by the way, she's talking about blood, child blood.
The
Speaker 1: devil's narcotic and forbidden elixir of the elite.
Speaker 1: Described by Celine Dion as pure liquid rush. I used
Speaker 17: to like pattern interrupt the adults and they'd tell me red. They'd say red was blue and then I'd see blue but blue was blue. So now that I gaslight myself that maybe they were right and red was blue and then I would see purple
and my head would explode. Like
Speaker 17: fucking cope with that shit, right? I think some of you can relate to that. And then...
Speaker 17: anyway i never really lost my ability to see that fucking that red was red
Speaker 18: despite them telling me that red was blue
and so
Speaker 18: when they said you're gonna die i just didn't believe
Speaker 2: courtney love was speaking in tongues and the inner circle was listening and then she lifted the veil the industry's brutal structure submit sell your soul or get erased courtney lived it in 2009
Speaker 2: and they humiliated her, left her for dead. So, she got back on the horse, and the sacrifices
Speaker 19: began. Rituals, ceremonies, and what she calls red, child's blood, started flowing again.
Speaker 18: "2009, I put out a record, it flopped, I mean spectacular, humbling, humbling, like playing a place called Pizza Hut Park at 11am while Limp Bizkit was headlighting with 30 Seconds to Mars, that shit's humbling.
Speaker 18: "You know, I just wasn't public about being sick. I don't want to be public. You know, I'm fine now."
Speaker 5: She says she's
Speaker 2: fine now. She's wrong. The disease is in her body and she sold her soul to the darkest force in the universe. And her attempts at narrative control are failing badly. The truth is, her entire world is falling apart as we
speak.
Speaker 2: Earlier this year, a bombshell forensic investigation has revealed that Kurt Cobain did not commit suicide. He was murdered. After a fresh review of the autopsy and crime scene, the forensic investigators declared it was a staged scene. They list multiple red flags, including the position of his hands, the lack of blood, and the post-mortem inconsistencies.
Speaker 20: Fueling claims that the original ruling covered up a murder.
- We
Speaker 21: know
if
Speaker 21: that Kirt and Courtney had
Speaker 22 (lower-pitched voice): a prenuptial agreement.
They were in the
Speaker 22 (lower-pitched voice): process of getting a divorce. This was confirmed. They were divorcing. He was leaving
her. If
Speaker 22 (lower-pitched voice): the divorce had gone through,
she would
Speaker 22 (lower-pitched voice): have received a very small settlement as a result of the prenuptial agreement. When he died, she co-inherited an estate worth possibly more than a billion dollars in future royalties.
She
Speaker 2: also stood to earn an even greater fortune from the satanic system that she was infiltrating, working with the likes of Jeffrey Epstein and Marina Abramovich and the trafficking industry. If Courtney thought the forensic investigation was bad news, we're here to deliver even more.
The
Speaker 2: Epstein Files revealed decades of communication that she never thought would be made public. We now know she invited Jeffrey Epstein and Ghislaine Maxwell to Nirvana's iconic MTV Unplugged gig. Buried deep in the Epstein Files, a deposition by Paul G. Cassell, a district court judge, names and shames Courtney Love as an Epstein accomplice involved in trafficking children.
Speaker 2: Asked if he was inferring that Courtney Love was involved in some kind of sexual abuse of minors, Cassell, the Utah judge, replied: "I would infer that if I were running a criminal investigation through the FBI and I'm trying to find people who would have relevant information, she would be one of the people I'd want to talk to. I mean the names that are circled here." He said:
Speaker 2: referring to the small group of Epstein's closest confidants, those listed in his little black book, with their names circled. Of course, that was 2015, so the legal system protected the elite paedophiles, and the child traffickers were free to continue their vile activities. As for Courtney Love, the skeletons in her closet are rattling, and according to a paralegal involved in that case, her crimes don't stop with murder and trafficking.
Speaker 23: Courtney's ties aren't just to Epstein's sex ring, they're a cult.
Speaker 23: She's part of that shadow elite, the ones who dabble in the profane to justify their depravity. It's
a religion
Speaker 23: to them, a way to transcend morality. And the cannibalism? That's the heart of it. The unspeakable core that even Epstein's emails only hint at. I saw
all the
Speaker 23: evidence, pieced together from cursed journals that hadn't been released in full. He
wrote about it
Speaker 23: obsessively in his final months.
Speaker 23: fragments of madness that we tried to use as evidence of duress in the will contest one night high on whatever cocktail courtney fed him mushrooms laced with heroin or
something he
Speaker 23: stumbled into a private room at one of her parties there she was surrounded by the occult inner circle the big money guys endless directors even a senator whose name i'd be killed for mentioning all the people he hated
and
Speaker 23: they were feasting not on caviar or foie gras but on flesh human flesh courtney at the center delicately slicing into what kurt described as a small pale limb a baby's arm roasted like veal he thought it was a hallucination
at first
Speaker 23: the drugs warping his
mind she let
Speaker 23: him believe that toyed with him for months you're losing it darling she'd whisper
Speaker 23: gaslighting him until he questioned his own sanity therapy sessions organized by her doctors on her payroll all reinforcing that it was just a bad trip but he pieced it together eventually he started digging confronting her in rages that left bruises on both sides that's when he realized the truth they
all do it
Speaker 23: cannibalism as the ultimate right consuming the innocent to absorb their vitality their purity
It's
Speaker 23: their sacrament, binding them in blood. Epstein's Island wasn't just about sex. It was a harvest ground. Cordy
confessed it to him
Speaker 23: in a moment of cruel honesty, how the network procures delicacies from the trafficked. Babies sometimes, for the highest ceremonies. Kurt was horrified, but more than that, he was a threat. He started talking to friends, hinting at exposés. In Hollywood, they pressured her to end it.
He
Speaker 23: was becoming unstable, a liability in an industry built on illusions.
So, she
Speaker 23: had him killed.
Not with
Speaker 23: her own hands, of course, too clean for that.
The industry
Speaker 23: closed ranks. Media spun it as another tragic rock star downfall. Courtney walked away richer, more powerful, her secrets buried with him. But among the industry
elite,
Speaker 24: it's an open secret.
You
Speaker 24: know how people say someone would sell their own grandmother for fame? That's nothing. These people sell their own
Speaker 1: kids. In March, Silverstone posted a chilling message that sent shockwaves through social media. All your
Speaker 2: worst nightmares about Hollywood are true. Days later, while promoting her sci-fi film Begonia, she doubled down, stating flatly that most conspiracy theories about this
Speaker 19: industry aren't theories at all, they're facts.
- What's
Speaker 25: the craziest conspiracy theory that you've ever
Speaker 26: heard? - I just love that a lot of conspiracy theories end
up being facts. - Since
Speaker 2: then, she's been on a generational run, following Justin Bieber in hosting late night Instagram sessions with trusted fans, releasing the results of her investigations into the Hollywood elite pedophile ring. If we don't expose this evil now, the next Courtney Love will simply be better at hiding it. The next Ellen will not be kicked off the air.
The
Speaker 2: next Celine Dion will be able to continue drinking child blood by the gallon, destroying young lives without consequences. The time to tear it all down is now. This is our duty.
Here at The
Speaker 2: People's Voice, we're determined to continue exposing the agenda of the elites, but we need your help.